<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>

	<help id="3">
		<text>Having trouble helping Bosh put the pictures in the correct place? Let him do the top row for you.</text>
		<solutionText>Bosh has worked hard and sorted out the top row of pictures, but you'll need work out the rest! Match the shapes of the remaining picture frames to the shadows on the wall!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>Without Bosh's help, sorting out these pictures will be harder.</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="4">
		<text>Need some help working out what to do?</text>
		<solutionText>Whoever stole that painting must have had a reason. If you want to ask Ink about it, you'll need to remember who the missing picture is of.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="4">
		<text>Are you missing some items?</text>
		<solutionText>Make sure you've explored the other rooms in the Palace. You never know what you might find! Why not have a look around the vault?</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="4">
		<text>Can't find the missing picture?</text>
		<solutionText>If you're searching for the missing picture, the Study would be a good place to start looking!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="4">
		<text>Can't work out what to do now?</text>
		<solutionText>What a strange picture! Apparently, Slosh has hidden a code to the vault in it. You should check in his book to find out how to decode it.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="6">
		<text>Are you struggling to provide Ink with the name of the missing portrait?</text>
		<solutionText>Have a  closer look in the Gallery. Once you've put all the other portraits back in their places, you'll see whose portrait is missing. Bosh may also be able to help!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="7">
		<text>Need some help searching the Study?</text>
		<solutionText>Slosh has a copy of the stolen picture hidden somewhere in the Study. Knowing him, you'll need to find a few things before you can get at it. Why not search the Study to see what you can find?</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="7">
		<text>Not sure what to do with the things you've found in the Study?</text>
		<solutionText>Slosh has a copy of the stolen picture hidden somewhere in the Study. Keep an eye out for somewhere you could use the crank and lever you found in the desk.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="11">
		<text>This kitchen is the perfect place to make a Sloshy, but you'll need a few things to do it. Need help finding out what they are?</text>
		<solutionText>Get Slosh's book from the library! It will have recipes in it. You'll need to put all the ingredients above the cooker.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="12">
		<text>Not sure where the ingredients are kept? Reveal their secret hiding places!</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="14">
		<text>Having trouble with your cooking? Making the cooking temperature lower will make it easier to judge your timing!</text>
		<solutionText>Cooking temperature has been reduced to make it easier to take your Sloshy off the heat before it gets too hot. We've even turned up the central heating so that your recipe cools down more slowly too!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>Cooking temperature has been set back to high. Be careful not to burn your Sloshy!</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="15">
		<text>Having trouble with your cooking?  A better pan will evenly spread the heat and make your recipe take less time to cook once it is up to temperature.</text>
		<solutionText>With these new pans, your Sloshy will take less time to cook once it is at the right temperature!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>You've downgraded your pan back to the basic model!</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="8">
		<text>The vault is a tough cookie to crack, and you'll never manage it without two special items. Need help finding out what they are?</text>
		<solutionText>Opening this vault will be tricky. To do it, you'll need to look at the missing portrait and find a book written by the Bin Weevil in the picture!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="10">
		<text>Having trouble with your code? Get some hints on how to find it!</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="18">
		<text>Is your gun not causing any damage?</text>
		<solutionText>Head to the kitchen! The freezing Sloshy needs to be made!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="19">
		<text>Are those Thuggs too much to handle? Slow them down a little with this upgrade.</text>
		<solutionText>The Thuggs will now take longer breaks between throwing water bombs at you.The Thuggs will now take longer breaks between throwing water bombs at you.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>The Thuggs have been revived and are back to their usual speed. Watch out for their water bombs!</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	
	<help id="20">
		<text>Is your water gun not freezing those Thuggs for long enough? Power it up with this upgrade.</text>
		<solutionText>Your water gun has been powered up! The Thuggs will now freeze for longer when you hit them. Good luck!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>Your water gun has been reverted back to its original less powerful state.</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="23">
		<text>Struggling to find a solution? See one possible solution.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	
</data>