<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>

	
	<help id="70">
		<text>Not found everything on this beach? Use this hint to help highlight everything you'll need.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="71">
		<text>Need a hand working out what to do here? Buy this upgrade and see what Flam's machine should look like when you're done.</text>
		<solutionText>Flam needs you to help her fix her machine before she'll work on your boat. 
There are quite a few bits missing, we've put them in place just for a moment so you know what to look out for. You're going to need to explore all the islands around here to find the parts. 
There's a curious snail on this island you might find useful elsewhere, so maybe you should take some of its food as bait.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="72">
		<text>Not found everything on this beach? Use this hint to help highlight everything you'll need.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="73">
		<text>Not found everything on this beach? Use this hint to help highlight everything you'll need.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="74">
		<text>Need a hand catching the fish for the stew?</text>
		<solutionText>The fish around these islands have some very specific tastes. They mostly feed on berries that have fallen into the water. You'll need to search around the islands to find 5 different tasty berries to catch the fish with. When you've got the bait, put it on the fisherman's hook.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="74" >		
		<text>Need a hand preparing the fish stew?</text>
		<solutionText>Now that you've caught the fish, you'll need to start the fire. Apparently, on one of the islands there's a very special kind of snail with a taste for spicy food. You'll need to lure one here somehow to help you start your fire.
		Finally, once the stew is cooked, you're going to need a container in order to take some stew with you. There's bound to be something you can use as a bowl on one of the nearby islands.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="75">
		<text>Need a hand finding some bits for Flam's machine?</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="76">
		<text>This island is full of useful items. Need a hand getting hold of them?</text>
		<solutionText>Explore the other islands and try to find an elastic band and something that can act as a pocket to put the ammo for the catapult in.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="76">
		<text>This island is full of useful items. Use this hint to help highlight everything you'll need.</text>
		<solutionText>To collect the items, first you'll need your catapult to get at them, then you'll need to go and collect them. In each case, we've marked either the item to collect or where you need to fire the catapult first.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="77">
		<text>The Recluse's challenge is pretty tough. Make it easier with this upgrade and reduce the number of rounds of hangman you need to win in order to gain the Recluse's help.</text>
		<solutionText>With this handy upgrade in place, you only need to win 2 consecutive rounds of hangman to gain the Recluse's help.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>Without this handy upgrade in place, you'll need to win 5 consecutive rounds of hangman to gain the Recluse's help.</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="78">
		<text>Having trouble knocking out those Thuggs? Use this upgrade to slow them down a little.</text>
		<solutionText>Now the Thuggs should take longer breaks between throwing their water bombs at you.  It should be much easier to take a decent shot at them. Just make sure you've seen the Recluse first to get a helping hand.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText>Without this upgrade in place, the Thuggs will take shorter breaks between throwing their water bombs at you. It should still be possible to beat them, but just make sure you've seen the Recluse for a helping hand.</toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="79">
		<text>You'll need to get Weevil X out of the way if you're going to thwart his plan. Need a clue on how to do it?</text>
		<solutionText>You can lure Weevil X onto the balcony by shutting down his satellite dish and hiding while he goes to investigate. Once he goes outside, hit the door release and he'll be locked out there while you work out how to save the day!</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="80">
		<text>Now that Weevil X is out of the way, you need to stop the laser. Need a clue on how to do it?</text>
		<solutionText>There should be a note around here with the panel release and target sequence codes on it. Use this key to help work out how to reprogram the satellite targeting.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
</data>