<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>

	<help id="50">
		<text>Need a hand finding all the hidden items in this area?</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="51">
		<text>Need a hand finding all the hidden items in this area?</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="52">
		<text>Need a hand finding all the hidden items in this area?</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="53">
		<text>This stone tablet is really tricky to put together! Would you like to see what it looks like when it's fully assembled?</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="54">
		<text>You'll need a few things set up in order to get the door code and distract the guard. This hint will help you work out what to do.</text>
		<solutionText>You'll need to use the binoculars to spy on the guard while he enters the door code. Grab the rubber band and coconut shell while he isn't looking to help you construct a catapult, and as for ammo... you'll need to find some berries somewhere and make them attractive to the flies somehow! Perhaps you should look around the places you've already been and see if you can find some flies annoying anyone.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="55">
		<text>Use this upgrade to reduce the number of infested trees you need to hit by doubling the number of nests in each tree!</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="56">
		<text>Need a hand working out how to get the door open? This hint will show you what the room should look like when you've solved the puzzle.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="57">
		<text>Need a hand working out how to get the door open? This hint will show you what the room should look like when you've solved the puzzle.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="58">
		<text>Need a hand working out how to get the door open? Get a clue on how to align the mirrors.</text>
		<solutionText>There is a cog with a handle on the floor. Why don't you see if you can use it to turn those cogs mounted on the wall? Line up the light beam with the door hatch.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="59">
		<text>Need a hand working out how to get the door open? This hint will show you what the room should look like when you've solved the puzzle.</text>
		<solutionText>Use your mouse to drag the pieces of the puzzle into place. You can't drag one piece through another, so you'll have to shuffle them around to get them all in order.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="60">
		<text>Need a hand working out how to get the door open? This hint will show you what the room should look like when you've solved the puzzle.</text>
		<solutionText>You'll need to position the main crystal carefully to split the light to both the pillars, then by standing at the base of each pillar you'll be able to reposition their mirrors to open the door.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
	<help id="61">
		<text>Solving this room takes quite a few steps. Need a hint on how to do it?</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>
</data>