<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>
	<help id="90">
		<text>Need a hand getting past those Thuggs?</text>
		<solutionText>Your water pistol is no match for the Thuggs, you'll need to be a bit more inventive. Try aiming at this light fitting instead.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
	<help id="91">
		<text>Need a hand getting past those Thuggs?</text>
		<solutionText>Your water pistol is no match for the Thuggs, you'll need to be a bit more inventive. Try aiming at the hanging plants instead.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
	<help id="92">
		<text>Need a hand re-wiring the lift control panel? This hint will show you a way to do it</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
	<help id="93">
		<text>Not sure how to fill up the vending machine? Use this hint to highlight where you should aim.</text>
		<solutionText></solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
	<help id="94">
		<text>Need a hint on how to rescue the hostages?</text>
		<solutionText>Using your new high powered water pistol you should be able to cut through the webs with ease. You just need to make sure you cut through the strands of web in the right order so that the hostage will swing into the arms of the waiting SWS agent.
		When you rescue Bunty, you need her to swing down and to the left, so cut the web on the right hand side and at the top and Bunty should swing to safety.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
	<help id="94">
		<text>Need a hint on how to rescue the hostages?</text>
		<solutionText>Using your new high powered water pistol you should be able to cut through the webs with ease. You just need to make sure you cut through the strands of web in the right order so that the hostage will swing into the arms of the waiting SWS agent.
		When you rescue Big Weevil, you need him to swing down and to the right, so cut the web on the left hand side and at the top and Big Weevil should swing to safety.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
	<help id="94">
		<text>Need a hint on how to rescue the hostages?</text>
		<solutionText>Using your new high powered water pistol you should be able to cut through the webs with ease. You just need to make sure you cut through the strands of web in the right order so that the hostage will swing into the arms of the waiting SWS agent.
		When you rescue Posh, you need her to swing down and slightly to the left, so cut the web at the top on the left and then at the top on the right hand side and Posh should swing to safety.</solutionText>
		<toggleOffText></toggleOffText>
	</help>	
</data>